me.com 2000-12-03

# Holiday Channel: St. Patricks Day

**Privacy Policy**

HolidayChannel.com is dedicated to providing you with quick and easy holiday solutions all within a safe and secure environment. We respect your right to keep your information confidential and are committed to maintaining your privacy while using our services and products. Personal information provided by you is treated with the utmost concern and security and will not be used in any manner you do not specifically authorize. This privacy policy applies to all information collected on the HolidayChannel site. 

********

HolidayChannel will not retain any of your personal information that you do not knowingly and voluntarily submit. To further ensure your privacy, our web server cannot automatically recognize information regarding your domain name or e-mail address when visiting our site.

When engaging in activities or conducting transactions at HolidayChannel you may be asked to supply personal information. Examples of such information include name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, gender, birth date, as well as other demographic or commerce related information. Using this collected information, we can provide you with a more personalized experience. We can use this information to occasionally notify you about important changes to our web site, new HolidayChannel services, and special promotions that we think you would find valuable. In addition, information about your previous purchases assists us in shaping our gift suggestions and helps us identify merchandise that might be of interest to you. We believe that by personally tailoring our services and products we can enhance your overall experience when visiting HolidayChannel.

Personal information you provide to HolidayChannel will not be disclosed to any third parties without your informed consent, with the exception that HolidayChannel may be obligated to disclose user information to comply with applicable local, state and federal laws, in cooperation with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities, or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. It is our policy not to sell, rent, or loan any of your personally identifiable information to any third party or outside affiliate.

We may share non-personal aggregate user information with our reputable business partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other trustworthy third parties. For example, we may tell a partner that X percent of women and Y percent of men use a particular HolidayChannel service without any identification of individual users.

You are free to correct, update, or remove any personal information previously given by visiting Account Information. 

****

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving and retrieving passwords used at the HolidayChannel site alleviating you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to HolidayChannel. We also use cookies to track items in your shopping cart and to save information regarding previous purchases. 

In addition cookies enable us to track visitor trends and patterns. We can then use this information to improve, update, or revise the features of HolidayChannel thus providing our visitors with more useful content and services. Cookies cannot be used by HolidayChannel to retrieve any credit card or personal information about you from your computer unless such information is knowingly and willingly provided by you. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to refuse all cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent.

****

We are committed to maintaining the highest level of security for all our guests' personal information. Once we receive the information you transmit to us we make every effort to ensure that such information is secure within our systems. When conducting online transactions we use the industry standard, SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption to secure the transmission of credit care information.

Your Holiday Club membership is password protected so only you may access your account and view the personal membership information. We recommend that you treat your password like other private pieces of information, such as an ATM pin number, and never divulge it to anyone. Employees of HolidayChannel will never solicit your password via telephone or e-mail. Consequently, any requests you receive for any kind of password information should be approached with extreme caution.

To further inhibit others from accessing your account we suggest signing out of your Holiday Club account and closing your browser when you have finished your work. This is especially important if using a computer that is accessible to others, if sharing a computer with others, or if using a computer in a public setting, such as a library.

****

To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of the following services: receiving information from HolidayChannel about new features or services, or receiving communications about offers from either HolidayChannel or third-party companies that offer a product or service that we think would be of value to you. To opt-out of such services or modify, update, or change any personal information please visit Account Information at any time.

Any information that you provide when purchasing products from any of our affiliated online partners may be used for marketing and promotional purposes and is subject to the opt-out policies of each individual partner.

****

The online protection and privacy of children is especially important to us. No information should be submitted online by guests under 13 years of age without the prior consent of their parent or guardian. Any personal information voluntarily provided by guests age 13 years and under with their parents' consent is used for the sole purpose of enhancing the interactivity of our site and Kids Zone services.

We NEVER make the personal information of anyone we know is under 13 years of age available to anyone outside of HolidayChannel unless required to do so by law.

When a child age 13 years and under registers for the HolidayChannel Elf Club we ask that he/she provide a parent's e-mail address so that we can alert the parent to their child's registration and subsequent activities. While children who register for the Elf Club do receive periodic newsletters such as the Elf Club News, any information collected from guests under 13 years of age is never used in any form for promotional or marketing purposes.

Children writing Santa are not required to have or supply his/her e-mail address. If a child does provide his/her email address s/he will receive a reply from Santa. It is our policy, however, not to send subsequent e-mail offers or promotions to children using the e-mail addresses provided for this purpose.

To further ensure the online safety of children a number of tools and resources exist to assist parents. Listed below are links that parents can use to better manage their child's online experience.

[SurfWatch  
](http://www1.surfwatch.com/)[Cybersavvy  
](http://www.cybersavvy.org/)[Cyberpatrol  
](http://www.microsys.com/)[Cybersitter  
](http://www.solidoak.com/)[Guardianet  
](http://www.guardianet.net/)[Net Nanny  
](http://www.netnanny.com/)[SOS KidProof  
](http://www.soskidproof.com/)[JumpStart for Parents  
](http://www.tenet.edu/jumpstart/parents.html)[Cybernetiquette Comix](http://disney.go.com/cybersafety/index.html)

****

By using our web site you consent to the terms and policies outlined above. We reserve the right to alter, update, or change these policies at any time, and such modifications will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes indicates your full acceptance of those changes.

****

We welcome your comments or suggestions. Please send your concerns to us at customercare@holidaychannel.com. For issues regarding your Holiday Club account please visit Account Information. For more information on how to contact us click here.

>> Click here to go back to the top.
